ARAWN DAVIES

Address · Phone

arawn@arawn-davies.co.uk · www.linkedin.com/in/arawn-davies· www.arawn-davies.co.uk

An efficient communicator and able to work in a team as both a leader and a team member, with extensive experience in many IT roles. I am an ambitious, highly motivated, and intelligent undergraduate student at De Montfort University who takes pride in delivering work to the best of my ability. With a kind, friendly and approachable personality, I take pride in providing excellent support to people. Highly proficient worker with 10 years using a vast range of different programming languages, software suites and hardware equipment, I can easily adapt and become familiar with any new platform used in my work.

SKILLS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Communication and thinking outside the box
- Linux, Git/GitHub, virtualization, UNIX (Linux/BSD/macOS) and embedded electronics (Arduino, Raspberry Pi)
- Experienced in IT, electronics, and ICT tutoring
- Experienced in languages C/C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML, PHP, x86 Assembly, and .NET.

EXPERIENCE

AUG 2021 - SEPT 2021

CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST, COMMUNITY BRANDS UK

- Provide customer support for several hundreds of schools across the UK
- Triaging technical issues with engineers and prioritize urgent cases.

JUNE 2015 - OCT 2021

DIRECTOR, ADX TECHNOLOGIES

- Provided specialist technical support for many different platforms, personal computing devices and networks
- Deployed software and installed hardware upgrades for client's computing devices.

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019

ELECTRICIAN + ENGINEERING WORKER, FREELANCE

- Worked in the local community in Harlech, North Wales.
- Helped build outdoor structures and installed telecommunications
- Provided other IT technical support for several local customers, both household and business.

FURTHER EDUCATION

OCT 2020 - PRESENT

COMPUTER SCIENCE BSC., DE MONTFORT UNIVERSITY

2nd Year grades (ongoing): Software & Security Management 89%, Object Oriented Design 89%, Web Application Development 90%, Data Structures & Algorithms 86%

1st Year modules: Computer Programming I/II, Computer Ethics, Computer Law & Cyber Security, Computer Systems, Mathematics for Computing, Database Design & Implementation

SEP 2017 - JUN 2019

A LEVELS, WYGGESTON QUEEN ELIZABETH I COLLEGE

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma (Distinction, Distinction, Merit) Equivalent of 3 A-levels at AAB

EDUCATION

SEP 2016 - JUN 2017

GCSES, REGENT COLLEGE

ICT (Distinction*), English (A*/B), Business Studies (B), Psychology (C)

SEP 2014 - JUL 2016

GCSES, WIGSTON COLLEGE

Certificate in Digital Applications (B), Electronics, Maths & Music (B), Double Science (B/C)

ACTIVITIES

JAN 2020 – MAR 2020

VOLUNTEER, LOROS SPIRAL SCRATCH

I volunteered at the local LOROS Hospice music charity store in Leicester, I authorized sales, aided in organization of donations, stock, listing and serving customers with any questions they may have.

SEP 2016 - PRESENT

AUDIO ENGINEER, FREELANCE

As a multi-instrumentalist, I combine my extensive IT software and hardware skills in addition to my music knowledge to provide digital audio workstation, computer & music audio equipment services to several local customers.

PROJECTS

CREATOR, MEDLI OPERATING SYSTEM

For almost a decade, I have been developing an operating system in my spare time for PCs in C# and .NET. This has been a major project of mine as it has aided in my learning and practical use of skills which I have learned over my career and education history. This can be seen at www.github.com/Siarantie-Solutions/Medli

CORE TEAM MEMBER, COSMOS (C# OPEN-SOURCE MANAGED OPERATING SYSTEM)

In addition to working on my operating system Medli, I have been working alongside a group of other highly experienced developers to develop a toolkit for other developers to create full fledged operating systems using existing applications and source code. This can be seen at www.github.com/CosmosOS/Cosmos

FOUNDER, SIARANITE SOLUTIONS

As an umbrella organization that manages Medli, I also use this organization to manage my other software projects that I have developed and created over the years. These include assembler byte-code virtual machines for embedded devices, compiler deployment scripts, and file systems for storing and managing data on storage devices. You can see a list of these projects www.github.com/Siaranite-Solutions

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Full UK Driving License
- DBS checked

References available upon request